MILAN BARANDE

Front end developer

milanbarande.com linkedin.com/in/milan-barande aithub.com/MilanBarande



75011 Paris, France milan.barande@gmail.com +33 6 31 27 24 31

ABOUT ME

I am a front-end developer with almost 5 years of experience. I care about UX, performances, code quality and accessibility. I enjoy teamwork and training junior developers.

I'm currently looking for a front-end (or full-stack JS) mission in remote. I can temporarily come to your office in Paris.

I am capable of working in french, english or german.

SKILLS



Node JS



Express JS







JavaScript

Typescript

Next JS

Redux

GraphQl







EDUCATION

2017 Le Wagon Full Stack web development

Le Wagon Montreal, Batch #77

2016-**Neuroscience** - Concordia University

2017 Research Assistant at the PERFORM Center

Sleep Lab

2016-**Neuroscience Microprogram** 2017 University of Montreal - Concordia U

2013-**Kinesiology Bachelor's**

2016 University of Montreal

EXPERIENCE



01/2021 - 06/2022

Front end developer Parfums Christian Dior

Freelance

Paris, France

08/2020 - 01/2021

Front end developer **Christian Dior Couture**

Freelance

Paris. France



04/2019 - 08/2020

12/2017 - 11/2019

09/2017 - 04/2019

Front end developer

Christian Dior Couture

Working on the front-end and GraphQL API of dior.com, an isomorphic app entirely written in functional programming and built with React, NextJS, TypeScript, Redux, ApolloGraphQL, recompose, rx-js...

Permanent contract

Paris. France

Freelance

Paris, France

Permanent

Paris. France

contract

LANGUAGE

FRENCH Mother tongue

ENGLISH

Fluent

GERMAN Fluent

PORTUGUESE Intermediate

Workshop Lead

Le Wagon

Occasionaly leading coding workshops at Le Wagon such as:

- Creating a landing page with HTML and CSS
- Introduction to JavaScript
- Introduction to React

Front end developer

Bluenove

Developing Assembl, an Open Source application that enables thousands of people to work together effectively on the definition of new ideas. Assembl's frontend is built with React, Redux, GraphQL, Sass, Jest, flow, webpack























HOBBY AND INTERESTS





